Guide to the Empire State Pride Agenda records, 1990-2013
Empire State Pride Agenda records, 1990-2013
- Series III. Media Relations and Communications
  - News Clippings
    - Albany Politics, July, December 2004 (Box 16, Folder 86)
    - Democratic and Republican Conventions, July 2004 (Box 16, Folder 87)
    - Hospital Visitations, August-October 2004 (Box 16, Folder 88)
    - Hevesi Pension Marriage Decision, October-November 2004 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - New York City Pension Fund, July-November 2004 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Network, August 2004 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Budget Legal Session, November 2004 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Trans Issues, February-July 2004 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Dignity and Safe Schools, March-September 2004 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings, December 2003-October 2004 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Gay Marriage Binder, June-July 2006 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Gay Marriage Binder, February-May 2007 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Flyers and Event Materials
    - Pride in the Pulpit
      - Testimony of the Reverend James Forbes, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 28)
      - Pride in the Pulpit, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 29)
        2 folders with informational materials
      - Religion and Homosexuality Materials, c. September- November 2004 (Box 17, Folder 30)
      - Religion and Homosexuality - Amici Briefs, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 31)
      - Relgion and Homosexuality - Amici Briefs, c. 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 32)
      - Pride in the Pulpit, 2004-2007 (Box 17, Folder 33)
        Various roundtable and informational materials
      - Rochester Roundtable, February 2005 (Box 17, Folder 34)
        Materials belonging to Chris Cormier
      - Albany Roundtable, March 2005 (Box 17, Folder 35)
      - Albany Roundtable, March 2005 (Box 17, Folder 36)
        Materials folder
      - Religion is Anti-Gay Advertisement, May 2005 (Box 17, Folder 37)
      - Emerging Face of Today's Activism, October 2005 (Box 17, Folder 38)
      - Chris Cormier - Pride in the Pulpi materials, October 2005; CD-5409 (Box 17, Folder 38)
      - Buffalo Roundtable, December 2005 (Box 17, Folder 39)
        Includes evaluation forms,
      - Buffalo Roundtable, December 2005 (Box 17, Folder 40)
      - People of Color Multi-Faith Roundtable, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 41)
      - Correspondence with Julian Bond, Chairman of the NAACP, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 42)
      - Pride in the Pulpit folder, Undated (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - General EPSA
      - Press Releases, 1996-1997; 2005-2007 (Box 17, Folder 44)
      - Lobbying, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 45)
      - "The Lesbian and Gay Health and Human Services Network", 1997 (Box 17, Folder 46)
      - Bill Clinton's Address to ESPA, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 47)
      - ESPA/ESPAF Activities on Behalf of LGBT Students, c. 2002 (Box 17, Folder 48)
      - General ESPA Fliers and Promotional Materials, c. 2006 (Box 17, Folder 49)
      - Empire State Pride Agenda Promotional Folder, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 50)
      - ESPA Strategic Plan, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 51)
      - Wall Street Journal Section on Philanthropy, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 52)
      - State Senator Shirley Hunley Letter writing Campaign, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 53)
      - Pride in the Workplace, Undated (Box 17, Folder 54)
      - Direct Mai, 1995, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Direct Mai, 1998-2000, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Direct Mai, 2006-2010 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Direct Mail (binder), 2004-2006 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Direct Mail (binder), 2007 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Stickers and Temporary Tattoos, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, Memos, Flyers, and Newsletters, 1989-2010 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - ESPA Volunteer Enterprise, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Gay Marriage, 2004, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Employee Benefits, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Ads in the Chief-Leader, 2007, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Equality at Work, 2010 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Presentation Notes, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
        Folded sheets from an oversized pad
      - Voters Guides, 1998-2012 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - New York State LGBT Health and Human Services Network - Annual Reports, 2004, 2006-2013 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - Loose Flyers and Programs, c. 2002-2009 (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - Loose Flyers and Programs, c. 2006-2013 (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Loose Flyers and Programs, c. 2006-2013 (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Election Campaign Flyers, c. 2004-2008 (Box 18, Folder 19)
      - In House Solicitations, 1999-2002 (Box 18, Folder 20)
        Section I of Binder
      - Acquisition Mailings, 1998-2002 (Box 18, Folder 21)
        Section II of Binder
      - Non-Development (Program) Mailings, 1999-2001 (Box 18, Folder 22)
        Section III of Binder
      - Stride with Pride: March on Albany Weekend, May 1991 (Box 18)
      - Leadership Briefing, 1995 (Box 18)
      - State of the State Reports, 1999-2001, 2003 (Box 18)
      - ESPA Fundraising Plan, 2003 (Box 18)
      - "One Year of Marriage Equality", 2005 (Box 18)
        by MassEquality
      - "An Ally's Guide to Talking about Transgender-Inclusive Non-Discrimination Laws", 2011 (Box 18)
        Found with photo materials in Box 22
      - "Injustice at Every Turn: A Report of the National Transgender Discrimination Survey", undated (Box 18)
      - "Advancing Transgender Civil Rights and Equality in New York", undated (Box 18)
      - "1, 324 Reasons for Marriage Equality in New York State" Report, undated (Box 18)
      - A" A blueprint for Meeting LGBT Heath and Human Services Needs in New York State, undated (Box 18)
      - Spring and Fall Dinner Programs, 2008 (Box 18)
      - Spring and Fall Dinner Programs, 2009 (Box 18)
      - Fall Dinner Programs, 2010 (Box 18)
      - Spring Dinner Program, 2011 (Box 18)
      - Spring Dinner Program, 2012 (Box 18)
      - Spring and Fall Dinner Programs, 2013 (Box 18)
      - Binder of Programs and Event Flyers, 1989-1998 (Box 19)
        Includes postcards, flyers, booklets, invitations etc.
      - Binder of Programs and Event Flyers, 1999-2002 (Box 19)
      - Binder of Programs and Event Flyers, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
      - Binder of Programs and Event Flyers, 2004-2007 (Box 19)
      - ESPA posters, advertisements, and event posters (Folder 1-2)
      - Matted articles, official recognition by the Governor on the 25 Anniversary of Stonewall, anti-discrimination posters. (Folder 3)
  - Slides and Photographs
    - Matted Photos from "The New York State LGBT Family Photo Album", Undated (Box 14)
    - Family Photo Project originals, c. 2008 (Box 18, Folder 23)
      From the New York City Album (for framed copies see Box 14)
    - Pride in the Pulpit Photo Album, ??? (Box 20)
    - Newsletter Photos - Roberta Skalr., 1997 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      Pictures taken while Earl was in Albany
    - Albany (with Matt), January 1998 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Legislative Reception, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Legislative Reception, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Fire Island Benefit Rites of Summer, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Gay Pride Albany, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Rochester Gay Pride Parade, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - SONDA - Albany Billboard, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Buffalo Brunch, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Legislative Reception, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Rochester Speak Out, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Jean Perry Conference, September 1997 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Rochester Major Donor, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Rites of Summer, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Lobby Day, undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
      Matt Foreman, ED
    - Lobby Day, undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
      Dick Dudley, ED
    - Lobby Day, March 2000 (Box 21, Folder 17-18)
    - La Bella Luna, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Buffalo Brunch, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Spring Dinner, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Lobby Day, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 22-24)
    - Buffalo Pride, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Tea Dance, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Legislative Reception, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 27-28)
    - La Bella Luna, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Lobby Day, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Fall Dinner, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 31-44)
    - Legislative Reception, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Performer, March 2005 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Tea Dance, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Fall Dinner, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 48)
      Mayor Guiliani, Senator Kennedy
    - White Party, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 49)
      Fire Island Grove
    - Albany Pride, Rochester Open House, Community Forum, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - New York City Pride, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - Fall Dinner, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 52)
      Ann Richards - Keynote Speaker
    - Buffalo, January 1998 (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - Marriage Press Conference, February 1998 (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - Family Brunch, March 1998 (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - Night 100, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 56)
      Ithaca and Loft
    - Night 100, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - Lobby Day, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - Health and Human Services Network, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 59)
    - Bill Signing - New York City Domestic Partnership Law, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 60)
    - Fall Dinner, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 61-63)
      Vice President Al Gore
    - Fall Dinner, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 64-65)
      President Bill Clinton
    - Tea Dinner, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 66)
    - Hilary Clinton Endorsement, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 67)
      New York City Hall - Human Rights Campaign and ESPA
    - Fall Dinner, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 68)
      First Lady Hilary Clinton
    - Hate Crimes Ceremony and Bill Signing, February 2000 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Programs, 2000-2001 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Events, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Board - Voter Guide, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Programs 1 & 2, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 5-6)
    - Matt and Tim, Undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Program and Events, Undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Unlabelled Dance, Undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Board, Undated (Box 22, Folder 10-11)
    - Board - Office, Undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Allan & Ralph, Undated (Box 22, Folder 13-14)
    - Scrapbook, Undated (Box 22, Folder 15-17)
    - Miscellaneous Photos, Undated (Box 22, Folder 18)
      People in the photo are identified on the reverse.
    - Unlabelled Photographs, Undated (Box 22, Folder 19-44)
    - Unlabelled Photographs, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 45)
      Possibly Pride in my Union
    - Unlabelled Contact Sheets, Undated (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Unlabelled Negatives, Undated (Box 22, Folder 47)
      One envelope of unlabelled prints.
    - Gay Pride, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - Scott Cranin for Town Board, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - Various Titles of Event Slides, Undated (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - Bayside, c. 2009; CD-2388 (Box 22, Folder 51)
    - Brockport and Brooklyn, c. 2009; CD-2389 (Box 22, Folder 52)
    - Brooklyn, c. 2009; CD-2390 (Box 22, Folder 53)
    - Buffalo, c. 2009; CD-2391 (Box 22, Folder 54)
    - Chelsea, c. 2009; CD-2392 (Box 22, Folder 55)
    - Geneva, c. 2009; CD-2393 (Box 22, Folder 56)
    - Ithaca, c. 2009; CD-2394 (Box 22, Folder 57)
    - Long Island and Brooklyn, c. 2009; CD-2395 (Box 22, Folder 58)
    - Nassau, c. 2009; CD-2396 (Box 22, Folder 59)
    - North Country, c. 2009; CD-2397 (Box 22, Folder 60)
    - Queens, c. 2009; CD-2398 (Box 22, Folder 61)
    - Rochester, c. 2009; CD-2399 (Box 22, Folder 62)
    - Suffolk, c. 2009; CD-2400 (Box 22, Folder 63)
    - Syracuse and Q Center, c. 2009; CD-2401 (Box 22, Folder 64)
    - Syracuse, c. 2009; CD-2402 (Box 22, Folder 65)
    - Upper West Side (Binai Jeshurun), c. 2009; CD-2403 (Box 22, Folder 66)
    - Upper West Side, c. 2009; CD-2404 (Box 22, Folder 67)
    - Westchester and Rockland, c. 2009; CD-2405 (Box 22, Folder 68)
    - LGTB Center, c. 2009; CD-2406 (Box 22, Folder 69)
    - Unlabeled, c. 2009; CD-2407 (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - Memorabilia
    - Pins(2) (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Stickers (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - T-Shirts(4) (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Roll of "Just Married" Ribbon, Undated; MU-1411 (Box 20)
    - Pins, Undated; MU-1403a-l (Box 23)
    - ESPA T-shirt, Undated; MU-1404 (Box 23)
    - Two ESPA Flags (blue), Undated; MU-1405-1406 (Box 23)
    - ESPA Flag (white), Undated; MU-1407 (Box 23)
    - Safe Schools Flag, Undated; MU-1408 (Box 23)
    - Equal Protection for Transgender New Yorkers, Undated; MU-1409 (Box 23)
    - 2011 Most Amazing Accomplishment Award, 2011; MU-1410 (Box 23)
    - ESPA pen, Undated; MU-1412 (Box 23)
- Series IV. Audio Visual and Digital Media
  - Videos
    - Alan Capelle Interview, July 28, 2003; Mini-DV V-7249 (Box 7)
      RT 27 min
      ESPA Number: 001
    - Dana Wageralcen & family, August 16, 2003; Mini-DV V-7250 (Box 7)
      ESPA Number: 004
    - Capitol Region B. Roll/Albany downtown & cityscapes (JP), August 23, 2003; Mini-DV V-7251 (Box 7)
      ESPA Number: 006
    - ESPA VHS Bump-Ups, 2003; Mini-DV V-7252 (Box 7)
      ESPA Number: 007
    - ESPA HQ NYC/ LGBT Comm. Center/ NYC Driving/ GMHC Website, September 16, 2003; Mini-DV V-7253 (Box 7)
      ESPA Number: 008
    - In the Life #309: Stonewall 25, June 28, 1994; 2003; Mini-DV V-7254 (Box 7)
      RT 57:42
      ESPA Number: 400
    - In the Life #402: Winter Episode February 1995, January 31, 1995; 2003; Mini-DV V-7255 (Box 7)
      with 30 sec. promo, RT 57:34401
    - In the Life #404: Summer Episode 1995, 2003; Mini-DV V-7256 (Box 7)
      RT 56:55, Full Mix on Audio 1&2
      ESPA Number: 402
    - In the Life #604: "American as Apple Pie", April/May 1997, 2003; Mini-DV V-7257 (Box 7)
      RT 57:40
      ESPA Number: 403
    - In the Life #1205, December 19, 2002; 2003; Mini-DV V-7258 (Box 7)
      RT 57:54
      ESPA Number: 404
    - In the Life #701: 6th Season Premiere- Back to School: Youth & Education, 2003; Mini-DV V-7259 (Box 7)
      RT 57:25
      ESPA Number: 405
    - In the Life #801, September 24, 1998/2003; Mini-DV V-7260 (Box 7)
      RT 57:10
      ESPA Number: 406
    - In the Life #802, December 1998, January 1999; 2003; Mini-DV V-7261 (Box 7)
      RT 56:12
      ESPA Number: 407
    - In the Life #1003: December 2000, October 23, 2000; 2003; Mini-DV V-7262 (Box 7)
      RT 55:45, Ch1 & Ch2: Stereo Mix
      ESPA Number: 408
    - In the Life #1007: April 2001, February 13, 2001; Mini-DV V-7263 (Box 7)
      RT 56:09, Ch1 & Ch2: Stereo Mix
      ESPA Number: 409
    - In the Life #1009: June 2001, April 17, 2001; Mini-DV V-7264 (Box 7)
      RT 58:44:09, Broadcast Version
      ESPA Number: 410
    - In the Life #1102: October 10, 2001, 2003; Mini-DV V-7265 (Box 7)
      RT 57:52:11, Component, Audio Layback, Master
      ESPA Number: 411
    - In the Life #1103: October 31, 2001, 2003; Mini-DV V-7266 (Box 7)
      RT 56:56:15, Component, Audio Layback, Closed Caption
      ESPA Number: 415
    - In the Life #1105: December 19, 2001, 2003; Mini-DV V-7267 (Box 7)
      Output
      ESPA Number: 413
    - In the Life #1109: "10th Anniversary Special", 2003; Mini-DV V-7268 (Box 7)
      RT 57:06, Closed Captioned
      ESPA Number: 414
    - In the Life #1202: "The Home Front", November 2002, September 27, 2002; 2003; Mini-DV V-7269 (Box 7)
      RT 56:22, Stereo/Audio Ch1 & Ch2
    - In the Life #1206, 2003; Mini-DV V-7270 (Box 7)
      RT 56:56, Stereo
      ESPA Number: 416
    - In the Life #1110, 2003; Mini-DV V-7271 (Box 7)
      RT 55:15
      ESPA Number: 417
    - In the Life #1107: "Comfort in Crisis", March 6, 2002; 2003; Mini-DV V-7272 (Box 7)
      RT 55:50, Air Master, Closed Captioning Line 21, Stereo Audio
      ESPA Number: 418
    - In the Life #1207: "Stealing Home", April 2003, February 28, 2003; Mini-DV V-7273 (Box 7)
      RT 54:33:04, Stereo/Audio Ch1 & Ch2, with ECO airdate
      ESPA Number: 420
    - In the Life #1209: "The Body Politic", June 2003, April 25, 2003; Mini-DV V-7274 (Box 7)
      RT 56:35, Stereo Audio Ch1 & Ch2
      ESPA Number: 421
    - Seven Days in September (BNN Film) on A&E, September 4, 2003; Mini-DV V-7275 (Box 7)
      Taped September 4, 2003, #1082
      ESPA Number: 422
    - Alan Van Capelle Interview, August 5, 2004; Mini-DV V-7276 (Box 7)
      Tape 1 of 2
    - Alan Van Capelle Interview, August 5, 2004; Mini-DV V-7277 (Box 7)
      Tape 2 of 2
      ESPA Number: 002
    - Gay Marriage, 2004; Mini-DV V-7278 (Box 7)
      Camera 1 Tape 1: Gay couples lined up to get married, NYC
      ESPA Number: 100
    - Rally, March 4, 2004; Mini-DV V-7279 (Box 7)
      Gay Marriage Rally/Protest, NYC
      ESPA Number: 101
    - GM Rally ESPA, March 12, 2004; Mini-DV V-7280 (Box 7)
      ESPA Number: 102
    - GM Rally ESPA, March 12, 2004; Mini-DV V-7281 (Box 7)
      ESPA Number: 103
    - ESPA 04- Brooklyn Pride, June 12, 2004; Mini-DV V-7282 (Box 7)
      ESPA Number: 104
    - NYC Pride '04, June 27, 2004; Mini-DV V-7283 (Box 7)
      Tape 1 of 3
      ESPA Number: 105
    - NYC Pride '04, June 27, 2004; Mini-DV V-7284 (Box 7)
      Tape 2 of 3
      ESPA Number: 106
    - NYC Pride '04, June 27, 2004; Mini-DV V-7285 (Box 7)
      Tape 3 of 3
      ESPA Number: 107
    - ESPA 04- E.E.B. Vote, June 28, 2004; Mini-DV V-7286 (Box 7)
      ESPA Number: 108
    - ESPA 04- E.E.B. Vote, June 28, 2004; Mini-DV V-7287 (Box 7)
      ESPA Number: 109
    - ESPA 04- E.E.B. Vote, June 28, 2004; Mini-DV V-7288 (Box 7)
      ESPA Number: 110
    - Sadie & Leslie Interview, August 12, 2004; Mini-DV V-7289 (Box 7)
      ESPA Number: 111
    - Gay Marriage, February 5, 2003; 2004; Mini-DV V-7290 (Box 7)
      NBC Morning w/ Katie Couric & Matt Lauer- Gay Marriage w/ Barney Frenk and Pat Buchanan, sandhogs story
    - ESPA 04, 2004; Mini-DV V-7291 (Box 7)
      Bush's 1st response/Alan VC reacting, WNBC/WABC & FOX w/ Bill O'Reilly talking on Senator Clinton's comments, Ross Levi on WTEN.WNYT/"Inside Albany", Alan VC vs. Cathrine Crier, "Inside City Hall" AVC vs. Joe Del.
      ESPA Number: 401
    - ESPA 04, 2004; Mini-DV V-7292 (Box 7)
      Ross Levi- WTEN- concerning MA legislature, Ross Levi- Capital 9 News- interview, Rochester Town Meeting WROC/WUHF, News- Bush on banning and constitutional amendments on same sex marriage, Same Sex Marriage w/ Alan VC- WRGB/WTEN, June 15th Defense of Marriage Act, May 17th Inside City Hall AVC
    - ESPA 04, 2004; Mini-DV V-7293 (Box 7)
      1986 Harvey Feirstien- on twice one w/out sound, ESPA sign, Jeff Soref, Stonewall after 25 years, mixed old footage
    - Queen's Pride, June 2004; Mini-DV V-7294 (Box 7)
    - ESPA Albany Day #1, May 24, 2005; Mini-DV V-7295 (Box 7)
      JP shot heading to Albany
    - ESPA Albany Day #2, May 24, 2005; Mini-DV V-7296 (Box 7)
      Morning Prayer/check-in, Des Glide, Tom Dwayne, Carmen
    - ESPA Albany Day #3, May 24, 2005; Mini-DV V-7297 (Box 7)
      Blind congressman, Pamela Barns M to F, Senator David Patterson, Senator Sheldon Silver, Youth Workshop
      ESPA Number: 003
    - ESPA Albany Day #4, May 24, 2005; Mini-DV V-7298 (Box 7)
      Briar McClaukin, The Whitbades- straight couple, Youths, AF Americans, Archbishop Richard Ray
    - ESPA Albany Day #5, May 24, 2005; Mini-DV V-7299 (Box 7)
      Queer Moms at podium, Mimi Goldman, Queer Youth, Road home
      ESPA Number: 005
    - ESPA Albany Day #6, May 24, 2005; Mini-DV V-7300 (Box 7)
      Queer Youth, Blind Rep's interview, Bear & Marvin, Carmen, Rev. Will speaker
    - ESPA Albany Day Tape 1, 2005; Mini-DV V-7301 (Box 7)
      MC- waiting for bus to leave, ride up to Albany
    - ESPA Albany Day Tape 2, 2005; Mini-DV V-7302 (Box 7)
      pulling into Albany, "mostly crap"
    - ESPA Albany Day Tape 3, 2005; Mini-DV V-7303 (Box 7)
      "mostly crap", Trans meeting at end
      ESPA Number: 009
    - ESPA Albany Day Tape 4, 2005; Mini-DV V-7304 (Box 7)
      Trans/Melissa Sklars, Youth in Action w/ Flyers
      ESPA Number: 010
    - ESPA Albany Day Tape 5, 2005; Mini-DV V-7305 (Box 7)
      "not so great footage until 15:00", bus home, Joe opens paper of Pride on bus, Transwoman Pamela Park part 1
      ESPA Number: 011
    - ESPA Albany Day Tape 6, 2005; Mini-DV V-7306 (Box 7)
      Pamela Park part 2, bus home
      ESPA Number: 012
    - Queen's Pride Tape 1, June 5, 2005; Mini-DV V-7307 (Box 7)
      ESPA Booth, cool shots of rainbow pinwheels, stickering
      ESPA Number: 013
    - Queen's Pride Tape 2, June 5, 2005; Mini-DV V-7308 (Box 7)
      ESPA Table
      ESPA Number: 014
    - Luncheon #1, June 8, 2005; Mini-DV V-7309 (Box 7)
      Pride in the Workplace
      ESPA Number: 015
    - Luncheon #2, June 8, 2005; Mini-DV V-7310 (Box 7)
      ESPA Luncheon, Pride in the Workplace, "Queer Eye for Straight Guy" celeb
      ESPA Number: 016
    - Brooklyn Pride, June 11, 2005; Mini-DV V-7311 (Box 7)
      ESPA Tabling, Lots of people "We are the Pride" Agenda, Anthony Wiener
      ESPA Number: 017
    - NYC Pride Tape 1, June 26, 2005; Mini-DV V-7312 (Box 7)
      Photo shoot, Press conference
      ESPA Number: 018
    - NYC Pride Tape 2, June 26, 2005; Mini-DV V-7313 (Box 7)
      ESPA Number: 019
    - Pre-Parade, June 26, 2005; Mini-DV V-7314 (Box 7)
      ESPA Number: 019B
    - NYC Pride Tape 3, June 26, 2005; Mini-DV V-7315 (Box 7)
      ESPA Number: 020
    - Hate Crimes Press Conference at City Hall, August 4, 2005; Mini-DV V-7316 (Box 7)
      ESPA Number: 021
    - Richie the Janitor/"I am the Pride Agenda" shoots, August 2005; Mini-DV V-7317 (Box 7)
      ESPA Number: 023
    - Stonewall Street Fair, August 13, 2005; Mini-DV V-7318 (Box 7)
      Street Fair, getting flyers signed
      ESPA Number: 024
    - Old ESPA Footage, 2005; Mini-DV V-7319 (Box 7)
      Dick, Jeff Soref, Tim Sweeney
      ESPA Number: 025
    - Old Stuff, 2005; Mini-DV V-7320 (Box 7)
      Press conference w/ Dick Dadey, 2 victims of Disc., Steve Senders, Gov. Cuomo
      ESPA Number: 026
    - Syracuse Tape 1, September 1, 2005; Mini-DV V-7321 (Box 7)
      ESPA Number: 027
    - Syracuse Tape 2, September 1, 2005; Mini-DV V-7322 (Box 7)
      ESPA Number: 028
    - "I am the Pride Agenda", 2005; Mini-DV V-7323 (Box 7)
      ESPA Number: 029
    - EJ Day Albany, May 8, 2006; Mini-DV V-7324 (Box 7)
    - EJ Day Albany, May 8, 2006; Mini-DV V-7325 (Box 7)
    - EJ Day Albany, May 8, 2006; Mini-DV V-7326 (Box 7)
    - EJ Day Albany, May 8, 2006; Mini-DV V-7327 (Box 7)
    - EJ Day Albany, May 8, 2006; Mini-DV V-7328 (Box 7)
    - EJ Day Albany, May 8, 2006; Mini-DV V-7329 (Box 7)
    - EJ Day Albany, May 8, 2006; Mini-DV V-7330 (Box 7)
    - EJ Day Albany, May 8, 2006; Mini-DV V-7331 (Box 7)
    - Around the Office, 2006; Mini-DV V-7332 (Box 7)
    - Luncheon, June 7, 2006; Mini-DV V-7333 (Box 7)
    - Equality at Work Luncheon Tape1, June 7, 2006; Mini-DV V-7334 (Box 8)
    - Equality at Work Luncheon Tape 2, June 7, 2006; Mini-DV V-7335 (Box 8)
    - Synagogue, May 30, 2006; Mini-DV V-7336 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 112
    - Synagogue Tape 1, May 30, 2006; Mini-DV V-7337 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 113
    - Synagogue Tape 2, May 30, 2006; Mini-DV V-7338 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 114
    - Pride Day 1, June 25, 2006; Mini-DV V-7339 (Box 8)
      Spitzer and Patterson
      ESPA Number: 115
    - Pride Day 2, June 25, 2006; Mini-DV V-7340 (Box 8)
      Rainbow flag, cool parade shots
      ESPA Number: 116
    - Pride Day 3, June 25, 2006; Mini-DV V-7341 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 117
    - ESPA Office, 2006; Mini-DV V-7342 (Box 8)
      Office Boxing Press stuff, Office Broll
      ESPA Number: 118
    - Rally at Sheridan Square 1, July 6, 2006; Mini-DV V-7343 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 119
    - Rally at Sheridan Square 2, July 6, 2006; Mini-DV V-7344 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 120
    - Rally #1, July 6, 2006; Mini-DV V-7345 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 121
    - Decision Day, July 6, 2006; Mini-DV V-7346 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 122
    - Alan at ESPA Tape 1, July 20, 2006; Mini-DV V-7347 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 123